poise.com 2013-11-27

# Privacy Policy | Poise®

Poise ® Privacy Policy

#### **Privacy**

This Site is owned, operated and maintained by KIMBERLY-CLARK CORPORATION ("Kimberly-Clark"). At Kimberly-Clark, we recognize that visitors to our Site may be concerned about the information they provide and how we treat that information. This Privacy Policy addresses those concerns. We may update the Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check in occasionally. There are specific regulatory requirements regarding online privacy protection for children under age 13. Please see the information under "Children" below.

#### **Information We Collect**

At this Site, you may choose to provide Kimberly-Clark with information about yourself that is "personally identifiable information". Your use of this Site may provide other information about you that is not “personally identifiable information”. Kimberly-Clark does not collect personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. You can visit this Site without telling us who you are or revealing information about yourself. However, if you give us personally identifiable information, such as, by asking to be put on our mailing list, we may contact you from time to time. Please note that any content posted by you onto this Site becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

#### **How Information is Collected**

Information is collected from you directly and with your knowledge. There are some features and functionality of this Site that require you to sign up to use them. If you do sign up to use such features, we use the information you supply for the purpose of providing the products, product information or services you request.

#### **What We Do with Your Information**

When you voluntarily sign up on this Site, we add your name, email address and street address to our mailing list. If you do not wish to receive these mailings, you may request to be removed from our mailing list by visiting this page, or by calling 1-888-525-8373. With your permission, we may share information such as your name, email address and street address with carefully selected companies ("partners") whose offers may be of interest to you. Your permission is given by "opting in" to programs with partners. Even if you "opt in", your date of birth, the dates of birth of your family members and credit card information are never shared. You may "opt out" of partner offers and programs at any time by updating your User Profile, Contacting us or calling 1-800-665-9773 (on weekdays during 8 AM to 4 PM Central Standard Time). Our partners are prohibited from using your contact information for purposes other than presenting relevant offers and programs, and they are required to maintain your contact information in confidence. Our Site sometimes includes notices of sweepstakes or other promotions we are conducting, and we may permit you to send your entry electronically in some cases. If that occurs, we will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion (i.e., to contact you if you're a winner).

#### **Interest-Based Advertising**

Kimberly-Clark participates in interest-based (on-line behavior) advertising. This means that you may see advertising on our website tailored to how you browse or shop, or you may see advertising for Kimberly-Clark products on other websites based on your browsing behavior across websites. Kimberly-Clark voluntarily participates in the Digital Advertising Alliance self-regulation program. As part of this self-regulation program, Kimberly-Clark supports deployment of the Advertising Option icon ("Ad Choices") in partnership with Evidon.

#### **Privacy for Mobile Applications**

You may choose to download mobile applications offered by Kimberly-Clark. If you use one or more of our mobile applications, the mobile application[s] collects certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use, the temporary or persistent unique device identifiers (sometimes called UDID) and information about the way you use the applications. The mobile applications also collect certain information you voluntarily provide, such as product information when you scan a bar code, and transactional information, such as when you make a purchase or respond to an offer. Our mobile applications may collect precise information about the location of your device, such as when you search for a store. However, you must first provide permission through your device before the application obtains such location information from technologies like GPS, Wi-Fi, or cell tower proximity (or a combination of these technologies). Mobile service providers may collect device-specific information, such as a unique device identifier, when you use our Site or one of our mobile applications.

#### **Updating Your User Profile**

We provide you the ability to exercise certain controls and choices regarding how we collect, use and share your personal information. By changing your User Profile or contacting us as described within this Privacy Policy, you may do the following: (1) You may correct, update and delete your registration account; (2) You may change your choices for subscriptions, newsletters and alerts; (3) You may choose whether to receive from us offers and promotions for our products and services, or products and services that we think may be of interest to you; (4) You may choose whether we share your contact information with partners so they can send you offers and promotions about their products and services; (5) You may choose whether to receive interest-based advertising; and (6) You may request access to the personal information we hold about you and that we amend or delete it and we request partners with whom we have shared the information do the same.

#### **Security Measures**

Kimberly-Clark takes precautions to protect your personal information. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, is collected on a web page enhanced with secure sockets layer protocol to protect the confidentiality of the data. No transmission of data over the internet or other public network can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. We make reasonable efforts to secure your personal information once we receive it, but we cannot guarantee the security of information you send to us.

#### **Notice to California Residents**

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Kimberly-Clark to partners for the partners' direct marketing purposes. With respect to these partners, this Privacy Policy applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please contact us by calling 1-800-665-9773 (on weekdays during 8 AM to 4 PM Central Standard Time).

#### **Children**

Kimberly-Clark is committed to protecting the online privacy of children and making the internet safe. Our Privacy Policy and practices reflect applicable laws and regulations on children's privacy. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. Any communication we get that is identified as being from a child under 13 will not be kept by Kimberly-Clark. We encourage parents or guardians of children under 13 to regularly check and monitor their children’s use of email and other activities online.

#### **Cookies**

Like many companies, Kimberly-Clark uses "cookie" technology on our Site. Cookies are information stored on your computer by your browser to save your preferences while you are visiting a particular site. When you log in, the cookie tells us whether you've visited us before or are a new visitor. The cookie doesn't obtain any personal information about you or provide us with any way to contact you, and the cookie doesn't extract any information from your computer. We do use the cookie to help us identify site features in which you have the greatest interest so that we can provide more of what you may want. We use pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These files enable us to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with us. With both cookies and pixels, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. If you do not enable cookies to be received by your web browser, you may not be able to access certain features and functionality on this Site.

#### **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us via via Contacting Us or phone us by calling 1-800-665-9773 (on weekdays during 8 AM to 4 PM Central Standard Time). For postal mail, please write to us at:

Kimberly-Clark Corporation  
P.O. Box 2020  
Neenah, WI 54957-2020
